LIUBOU USHAKOVA

DATA ANALYTICS | DATA ENGINEERING | DATABASE MANAGEMENT

CONTACT

646 942 3333

Liubou.ny@gmail.com

Scotch Plains, NJ 07076

liubou-ushakova-7b4716a2

KEY SKILLS

Data cleaning | Data Visualization | Web Scraping | Data Storytelling | Dashboard Design | KPI reports

Data Warehousing |
Databases | Data Modeling |
ETL Processes

SQL | Python Programming | Tableau Desktop | Snowflake | Streamlit

MS Excel | Adobe Photoshop

EDUCATION

MASTER OF ARTS (M.A.): Illustration – Vitebsk State University, Vitebsk, Belarus 2010-2011

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS (B.A.): Graphic Design, Technical Illustration – Vitebsk State University, Vitebsk, Belarus 2005-2010

Tableau Desktop Specialist Certification

COURSES

Data Warehouse – The Ultimate Guide • Udemy

Snowflake – The Complete Masterclass • Udemy

PostgreSQL – The Complete SQL Masterclass • Udemy

Data Engineering with Python and SQL • Udemy

PROFILE

Focused beginner data analyst/data engineer/database administrator delivers consistent and professional work for every assignment. Willing to take on any task to support the team and help business succeed. Offers strong data related technical skills in SQL and Python Programming. Experienced in deriving and visualizing meaningful insight from data. Good at troubleshooting problems and building successful solutions.

EXPERIENCE

3D GENERALIST • SEPTEMBER 2015 – JULY 2022 SWEETPIXELS LLC • BROOKLYN, NEW YORK

- Optimized 3D assets for efficient real-time rendering performance.
- Streamlined 50 % of all art processes, workflows and pipelines with content and tools teams.
- Refined, changed and optimized art in collaboration with lead artists.
- Delivered final assets according to project deadlines while maintaining consistency in quality across all deliverables.
- Developed multimedia presentations and other collateral for use in different products, presentations and production works.

LEGAL SECRETARY • FEBRUARY 2013 – AUGUST 2015 LAW OFFICE OF OLGA SKLYUT • BROOKLYN, NEW YORK

- Systemized meticulous diary entries, journals and statistical data (more than 10K records).
- Coordinated delivery of legal correspondence to clients, witnesses and court officials.
- Maintained 100 % client files by ensuring proper organization and accessibility of all relevant materials.
- Ensured accurate filing of legal documents both physically and electronically.
- Assisted with daily case management and preparation, organizing exhibits and files for senior legal staff (35 + daily cases).

IT SUPPORT SPECIALIST • SEPTEMBER 2005 – APRIL 2012 CROMTEL INC • VITEBSK, BELARUS

- Diagnosed and resolved technical hardware and software issues for 6+ years.
- Arranged equipment for employee use, ensured proper installation of cables, operating systems and appropriate software.
- Proved exceptional service to 25+ customers, actively listening to concerns and addressing them promptly, increasing overall productivity by 20%. Guided users with troubleshooting using diagnostic tools.

PROJECTS

DAILY PROFIT/LOSS STATEMENT ANALYSIS • JUPYTER NOTEBOOK • PYTHON

https://github.com/LiubouNY/Daily_Profit_Loss_Statement_Graph_Python

GLOBAL LAYOFFS • POSTGRESQL • TABLEAU PUBLIC

https://github.com/LiubouNY/PostgreSQL_Data_Cleaning_And_Exploratory_Analysis https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/liubou.ushakova/viz/GlobalLayoffsAnalysis_1715611 8244910/Dashboard1

COVID-19 TWEETS SENTIMENTAL ANALYSIS • JUPYTER NOTEBOOK • PYTHON

https://github.com/LiubouNY/Covid-19 Tweets Analysis